(Leonard:)Penny's not answering my texts.
(Bernadette:)Who cares?
Focus on the game.
(Leonard:)This stupid game is why
she's mad in the first place.
(Leonard:)-I'm telling her I'm quitting.
-No!
(Bernadette:)Quitting would be the worst thing
for your relationship.
(Howard:)Why?
(Bernadette:)Because it would make you seem like
something she already thinks you are.
(Leonard:)-What does she think I am?
-How do I put this?
(Bernadette:)She's been known to call you a name
that usually applies to a lady part.
(Bernadette:)Or a cat.
(Bernadette:)Or a willow.
(Leonard:)I can't believe
she would say that about mo.
(Bernadette:)If you're gonna cry about it,
theres tissues in my purse.
(Bernadette:)Unless you got some in yours.
Big willow.
J' (SINGING NEIL DIAMOND'S
"AMERICA") J'